hashimotosinstitute.com 2015-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Hashimotos Summit

**PRIVACY POLICY** ****

We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all of our users while offering the highest quality user experience. By using www.hashimotosinstitute.com (the “Website”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Because we gather certain types of information about and from you, we believe it is important that you understand our collection and use of this information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather, how we use it, how to correct or change it, and what steps we take to safeguard personal information provided to us both online and offline. Please read the complete Privacy Policy below, as well as our Terms of Use, and contact us if you have any questions.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?**

You can visit our Website, read materials, and browse the Website’s contents without giving us any personally identifiable information. In order to provide you with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service and attention, and to accommodate certain requests which you make, we request information about you in certain circumstances and collect certain information automatically.

**Information You Volunteer**

We collect personally identifiable information that you enter on the Website or otherwise volunteer to us (such as your name, e-mail address, credit card number, home address, phone number, and/or similar information), when you contact us to, among other things, make purchases or request information. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future experiences for you, improving our operations, and communicating with you.

******Information Collected Automatically**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many web sites, we use “cookies” and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our Website or advertisements and other content served by us or on our behalf on other web sites. We may also automatically collect your Internet Protocol and referring web site addresses, browser type and domain name. This information helps facilitate your online experience on our Website. We use “cookies” to track usage patterns on our Website and to control the display of ads, as well as to offer other functionalities. You can turn off cookies, but that will affect your online experience. Please see below for more detail on cookies.

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?**

We use collected information to evaluate and administer our Website, fulfill your requests, respond to any future problems, such as difficulties in navigating our Website or accessing certain features, and to gauge user trends.

As in any transaction, when you purchase products or make a donation by credit card, your credit card company will have all relevant information about the name of the vendor, item(s) purchased, date, total cost and other information necessary to process the transaction. We will not otherwise provide any personal data to your credit card company without your permission. We and our technical and fulfillment agents, partners and consultants follow carefully proscribed procedures to safeguard credit card data in connection with your transactions and adhere to certain legal requirements.

**HOW DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Personal information is available to us and the technical and fulfillment agents, partners and consultants who make our Website available to you. Anonymous information is available to our affiliates, sponsors and partners.

Basic information is shared with the speakers we partner with to for the purpose of supporting you through the interviews and beyond.

When you sign up for our telesummit, your name and email address are shared with the Hosts/Producers-only of our summit.

You may receive occasional emails from Dr. Alan Christianson, NMD of [www.integrativehealthcare.com](http://www.integrativehealthcare.com/), Andrea Nakayama of [www.ReplenishPDX.com](http://www.replenishpdx.com/) and Dr. Izabella Wentz, PharmD from [www.thyroidpharmacist.com](http://www.thyroidpharmacist.com/).

We don’t share your information with any third party outside of our organization, except for the fulfillment of an order.

Website hosting firms, technical and database consultants, advertising agencies, order processing partners, and other third parties may have access to personally identifiable information in the course of making our Website and its contents available. All companies working for and with us must comply with our privacy policies, and are not permitted to sell your information to third parties or to use it except as authorized by us and you, or as permitted or required by law.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AND OUR USE OF SUCH INFORMATION**

The following describes the types of personal and other information we may collect about you, and how we use and maintain that information:

We may collect personal information about users. Any personal information (e.g., name, e-mail address, or otherwise) provided by such users may be used by us or our respective affiliates, employees, agents, third-party content providers, third-party service providers, technical providers, or licensors, if any, as they may determine, without any compensation or consideration to the user. Further, by a user submitting content to The Hashimotos Institute, which may include the user name, photos, text, or otherwise, such user grants The Hashimotos Institute the right to review and categorize such content.

We also reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent for the following purposes: as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our Website and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation.

**HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?**

Your web browser offers so-called “cookies” which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a web site. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. However, cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best and make it easier to use our Website. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser. Our Website is viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features or offerings will not be available to you.

**HOW CAN YOU CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

You may unsubscribe to any of our online e-mail updates by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any e-mail message. We will take commercially reasonable steps to implement your opt-out requests promptly; but you may still receive promotional information from us by mail for up to 60 days due to printing and mailing schedules, and up to 10 days for e-mail. You may also continue to receive information from those third parties to whom your information was previously disclosed.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We incorporate standard industry practices internally and with our service providers, which we believe suits the degree of sensitivity of the information involved to maintain the security of your personal information and to avoid its disclosure except as described in this Privacy Policy.

Although we have implemented systems and procedures to secure the data maintained by us, security during Internet transmissions can never be assured. Our policy is to limit access to personal data to those employees or agents with a specific need to access or retrieve this information. We store data on multiple service systems, in controlled environments. To maintain security, we conduct internal reviews of our security measures on a regular basis.

**VISITORS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

Our Website and the servers that make this Website available worldwide are located in the United States. The Internet laws in the United States govern all matters relating to this Website. Any information you provide in subscribing to our Website or registering or ordering at our Website will be transferred to the United States. By visiting our Website and submitting information, you authorize this transfer, processing and use.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the Privacy Policy when you visit our Website to be sure that you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy, or in how we use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make any retroactive material changes in how we handle previously collected personal information unless you allow us to do so, or unless we are legally required to do so, and in such a case we will e-mail registered Website visitors information on material changes to this Privacy Policy.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit our Website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Texas. If you have any concern about privacy at our Website, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. As our business changes, our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use may change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of personal information collected in the past without the consent of affected user.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

We are strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who visit our Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under 13 and have adopted techniques to ensure compliance with this Privacy Policy and the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”). COPPA and its accompanying regulations under United States federal law protect the privacy of children using the Internet. Our Website includes content that we believe to be unsuitable for children under 13 and which are not necessarily monitored. We encourage all parents to talk to their children about online safety and to monitor their children’s use of the Internet.

**GOVERNING LAW**

By choosing to visit our websites or otherwise provide information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this privacy policy will be governed by the law of the State of Arizona. You also agree to arbitrate such disputes and to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Use or other agreement we have with you.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please e-mail us at support@beyondtheordinaryshow.com. Please include the URL of the Website involved in your request.

Or you can contact us by mail at:

9200 E Raintree #100  
Scottsdale, AZ 85260
